Guide to the Robert F. Pannett papers, [ca. 1948-1994]
Pannett, Robert F. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert F. Pannett papers, [ca. 1948-1994]
37-5-4087
Pannett, Robert Francis
3.4 cubic feet.
Correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Letters to and from Robert Pannett when he was at Cornell, 1948-1954, other correspondence, miscellaneous pictures and other items relating to Cornell.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Robert F. Pannett graduated from Cornell with a B.A. in Applied Physics in 1952 and an M.S. in Applied and Engineering Physics in 1954. After graduating, he worked for McDonnell Aircraft as project manager for the Gemini IV capsule. Papers relating to his career are held by the University of Houston.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Letters to and from Robert Pannett when he was at Cornell, 1948-1954, other correspondence, miscellaneous pictures and other items relating to Cornell.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pannett, Robert Francis, 1931-; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University; Cornell University. Class of 1952.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Daily Goals, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Congrats for getting into Cornell, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Letters from Bob at Cornell to family, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Letters from Bob at Cornell to family, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Letters from Bob at Cornell to family, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Letters from Bob at Cornell to family, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Letters from Bob at Cornell to family, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Memos and photographs documenting summer trips taken with family, June 1952 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Letters from Bob at Cornell to family, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Letters from Bob at Cornell to family, 1953, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Letters from Bob to family, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bob's letters from Cornell to others, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bob's letters from Cornell to others, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bob's letters from Cornell to others, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Letters from Bob to Mr. & Mrs. Abbott, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Letters - Cornell, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Letters - Cornell, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Letters - Cornell, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Letters - Cornell, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Baptist Student Center - Cornell, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Testing/recognition/awards, 1948, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Selective Service, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Cornell Dramatic Club, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Cornell Club, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Telegrams, 1951, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Radio Corporation of America, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- IBM, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bell Telephone Laboratories, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- McDonnell Aircraft job offer, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Job offers/summer jobs, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Communication of Bob after College, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Communication to Bob as Cornell College Rep., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cost at Cornell, 1950-1955 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Math Puzzles (Disabled American Vet. Service Foundation), 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Orientation/Activities/Maps, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Graduation, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Pictures of Cornell, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Postcards - Cornell, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Cornell Alumni News, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Albert C. Murphy Scholarship grant, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Engineers' Day, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Music/Sage Chapel/choirs, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Photos of Mary Jane and C. Richard Evenson, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Grades, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Misc. items, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Letters from parents, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Letters from parents, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Letters from parents, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Letters from parents, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Letters from parents, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Letters from parents, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Letters from parents, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Letters from parents, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Letters from parents, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Letters from parents, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Letters from parents, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Letters from parents, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Letters from parents, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Letters from parents, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Letters from parents, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Letters from parents, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Letters from parents, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Letters from parents, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Letters from parents, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Letters from parents, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Letters from parents, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Letters from parents, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Letters from parents, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Letters from parents, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Letters from parents, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Letters from parents, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Letters from parents, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Letters from parents, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Letters from parents, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Letters from parents, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Letters from parents, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Letters from parents, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Letters from parents, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Letters from parents, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Letters from parents, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Letters from parents, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Letters from parents, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Letters from Constance Abbott, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Letters from Constance Abbott, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Letters from Constance Abbott, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Letters from Constance Abbott, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Letters from Constance Abbott, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Letters from Constance Abbott, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Letters from Constance Abbott, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Letters from Annamama, 1950, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Letters from Sister and Brother, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Letters from Richard and Helen Evenson, 1949-1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Letters from J. B. Nance, 1951,1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Letters from Sigurd Dahl and unknown, 1946-1948 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Letter from Kermit Meckert, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Letters from H. Logan Cobb, 1944,1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Letter from Eugene Clark, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Letter from David to Parents, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Letters from other family members, 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Thesis: A Transistor Integrator, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Applied and Engineering Physics at Cornell, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Autobiography of Robert Pannett (Box 4, Folder 18)